<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="app_name">Magnus Edutech</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="hello_world">Hello world!</string>
    <string name="drawer_open">Slider Menu Opened</string>
    <string name="drawer_close">Slider Menu Closed</string>
    <string name="loading_video">Loading ...</string>
    <string name="aboutUSHeader">About Us</string>
    <string name="about_us">When Lord Buddha was undergoing “Mahaparinirvana”
        in the shadow of a Saal tree at Kusinagar on a full moon day, his disciple Anand was weeping over Buddha’s departure and told him thus, “ Dear Lord! You are leaving me in the midst, and I haven’t become enlightened (Arihant) yet, what will happen to me?
        The world will be absolutely dark for me. You were the light.... Have compassion on us”\n
        Buddha opened his eyes, gave the last dictum, “ Ap Deepo Bhava”, meaning,
        “Be your own guiding light Anand. Nobody can be the light for you”.\n
        The Genesis of “Magnus Edutech” has its emotional bondage with the Buddhist
        dictum on Ethics “Ap Deepo Bhava”- Be your own guiding Light.
        The pedagogy of “Teach Yourself through SAVE (Smart Audio Video Education)” is an innovative and
        a well tested methodology of Magnus Edutech, developed by a senior civil
        servant with more than two decades of work experience.\n
        These days, we see a huge crowd of Civil Services’ Aspirants rushing to Delhi in quest of the
        right knowledge and guidance. Quite a few get distracted in the vagaries of the city life,
        intimidated by a plethora of unnecessary guidance, and thus loosing their focus and missing their target.
        The failures bring to them a sense of frustration.\n
        Moved by the plight of the young bright minds, we at Magnus Edutech,
        have devised an innovatively improvised take on the methodology of teaching through
        “Smart Audio Video Education” complemented with written concise key notes depicting
        key concepts and key words. This approach has delivered remarkable results as experienced
        from full-fledged trials with several students. In fact, with this methodology, the students
        find themselves more equipped than any other method to face the challenges in the Civil Services
        examination. Before bringing this concept to you, much research work has been done on the pedagogy,
        content of lectures, standard of keynotes and other aspects. The most important aspect, which has been
        the central theme of the Audio- video classes, is that the students must find themselves
        equipped to present their viewpoints in a more analytical manner within the limited time-span of
        the examination. Based on an extensive research, we have come to observe, that “What not to be studied?”,
        “ How can a student maximize his marks by spending minimum amount of time?”Since the class has
        been developed by a seasoned civil servant with more than 20 years of work experience and teaching,
        much hard work has been made to maintain the quality of the lectures vis-a-vis the aspirations of the
        budding civil servant. With this methodology, students will have the ease to learn at their own pace.
        They will be in position to revise the course within a short span of time, and can analyze their improvements
        at regular intervals in a more scientific manner.
        Moreover, they will not be constrained to experience the dehumanized environment of classroom teaching.\n
        To provide you with a snag-free technical support, we have a well-experienced team of young IITians,
        thus ensuring your learning process continues without any hassles and you become your own light !
    </string>

    <string name="contact_us">
    Magnus Edutech
    \nBakhtawar Singh Block,\nAsian Game Village,\nDelhi - 110049\nPhone : +91-9643984795, +91 9953644108
    \nE-mail : magnusedutech@gmail.com\nWebsite : magnusedutech.org\n
    </string>

    <!-- Nav Drawer Menu Items -->
    <string-array name="nav_drawer_items">
        <item>Home</item>
        <item>Resources</item>
        <item>About Us</item>
        <item>Contact US</item>
    </string-array>

    <!-- Nav Drawer List Item Icons -->
    <!-- Keep them in order as the titles are in -->
    <array name="nav_drawer_icons">
        <item>@drawable/menu_home_active</item>
        <item>@drawable/menu_resource_active</item>
        <item>@drawable/menu_about_us_active</item>
        <item>@drawable/menu_contact_us_active</item>
        <item>@drawable/ic_home_active</item>
        <item>@drawable/ic_home_active</item>
    </array>

    <!--Home Icon -->
    <array 	  name="course_icon">
        <item>@drawable/icon_1</item>
        <item>@drawable/icon_2</item>
        <item>@drawable/icon_3</item>
        <item>@drawable/icon_4</item>
        <item>@drawable/icon_5</item>
        <item>@drawable/icon_6</item>
        <item>@drawable/icon_7</item>
    </array>
    <!-- Content Description -->
    <string name="desc_list_item_icon">Item Icon</string>
    <string name="title_activity_contact_us">ContactUs</string>
    <string name="exitMessage">Press enter again to exit.</string>

    <!--  Addition by jugal  -->

    <string name="emailAddress">Email</string>
    <string name="forgetPassword"><u>Forget Password</u></string>
    <string name="password">Password</string>
    <string name="SignIn">Sign In</string>
    <string name="messageSignUp">Not a member? Sign Up Now</string>
    <string name="signUp">Sign Up</string>
    <string name="loginOptions">Login Using</string>
    <!--Registration fields -->
    <string name="userName">Full Name</string>
    <string name="userMobileNumber">Mobile No</string>
    <string name="confirmPassword">Confirm Password</string>
    <!--Error Msg registration-->
    <string name="err_msg_name">Enter your full name</string>
    <string name="err_msg_email">Enter valid email address</string>
    <string name="err_msg_phone">Enter valid phone number</string>
    <string name="err_msg_password">Password should contain at least 6 characters.</string>
    <string name="err_msg_confirm_password">Enter the confirm password</string>
    <string name="err_msg_confirmation">Password and confirm password does not match</string>
    <!-- Home fragment : -->
    <string name="NoCourseFoundHF">No result found! for </string>

    <!--Resource fragment-->
    <string name="comingSoon">Coming soon ...</string>

    <!--Server -->
    <string name="err_server_header">Server error!</string>
    <string name="err_server_body">Server is not responding</string>
        <!--server Login error-->
    <string name="err_login_header">Login error!</string>
        <!--server Login error-->
    <string name="err_registration_header">Registration error!</string>
    <!--Forget Password-->
    <string name="forget_password_prompt_header">Forget password </string>
    <string name="err_forget_password">Either the email is not valid or server is not responding </string>
    <string name="success_forget_password">Password has sent to the entered email. </string>


    <!--Alert Button-->
    <string name="alert_ok">Ok</string>
    <string name="alert_cancel">Cancel</string>
    <string name="alert_submit">Submit</string>

    <!--Activity pricing String-->
    <string name="packageOneSub">Subscribe for 6 months</string>
    <string name="packageTwoSub">Subscribe for 12 months</string>
    <string name="packageThreeSub">Subscribe for 18 months</string>

    <string name="packageOnePrice">Price : 7500/-</string>
    <string name="packageTwoPrice">Price : 12500/-</string>
    <string name="packageThreePrice">Price : 17000/-</string>

    <string name="buy">Buy</string>




</resources>
